http://www.sdcivic.org/privacy

A Message From San Diego Theatres
Skip to main content
More Info
Virtual Event
Sun, Dec 20, 2020 @ 2:00PJim BrickmanComfort & Joy at Home LIVE! VirtuallyBuy ticketsBuy ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Tue, Jan 19 – Sun, Jan 24, 2021Hadestown:
RescheduledRescheduled (Dates TBA)Rescheduled (Dates TBA)More Info
Balboa Theatre
Tue, Jan 19 & Wed, Jan 20, 2021 @ 7:30PThe Office!: CanceledA Musical ParodyCanceledCanceledMore Info
Civic Theatre
Tue, Mar 2 – Sun, Mar 7, 2021Les Misérables:
RescheduledGet season ticketsGet season ticketsMore Info
Balboa Theatre
Fri, Mar 5, 2021 @ 7:30PThe Simon and Garfunkel StoryBuy ticketsBuy ticketsMore Info
See Full Calendar
Plan Your VisitBalboa TheatreParkingSeating ChartSafety & SecurityFood & BeverageAccessibilityPhotosCivic TheatreParkingSeating ChartSafety & SecurityFood & BeverageAccessibilityPhotosBoth theatres are in downtown San Diego within 0.3 miles of each other (6 minute walk)Venue RentalBalboa Theatre360i TourPolicy, Rules & RegsTechnical SpecificationsCivic Theatre360i TourPolicy, Rules & RegsTechnical SpecificationsBoth theatres are in downtown San Diego within 0.3 miles of each other (6 minute walk)About UsHistoryBalboa Theatre HistoryCivic Theatre HistoryLeadershipBoard of DirectorsLeadership TeamMission, Vision & ValuesBackstage Pass BlogSan Diego Theatres manages both the Historic Balboa Theatre and the San Diego Civic TheatreGiving
Privacy Policy
Customer Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting SanDiegoTheatres.org, SDBalboa.org and SDCivic.org. San Diego Theatres respects the privacy of our customers and the users of our website. We want to provide you with explicit information on how We collect, use, share and retain information whenever you purchase tickets to San Diego Theatres Shows, telephone, fax or donations, sign up to receive email notifications from or about Us, visit and provide information in a public forum, or visiting our website. By visiting SanDiegoTheatres.org, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
We may change this Privacy Policy. We will also change the "Last Modified" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. You should periodically review this Privacy Policy. Use of SanDiegoTheatres.org by you following such notification and/or consent constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as modified.
Information We Collect
We collect information about our customers and users of our websites in various ways, such as your voluntary submissions, including when you purchase tickets through us or our business partner Ticketmaster, by registration of your information to create a membership account or receive information from us, by visiting our social networking sites, and through cookies and other tracking technologies. When you purchase tickets through San Diego Theatres or Ticketmaster, you can opt-out of the sharing of this information.;
We do have an email sign-up on our website, and the information provided is maintained on San Diego Theatres’ Archtics ticketing platform. Any transactions on the Ticketmaster website are covered by Ticketmaster's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
We also may collect information from our business partners. We may also provide information to our presenters for their events only. If we collect your information through sweepstakes and/or contests, we only do so after you have opted-in to receive additional information from us. We do not purchase information about you nor do we sell your information.
We may combine the information we receive from our business partners with information that we have obtained about you. The type of information we collect is described in more detail below.
Personally Identifiable Information
When you visit our website, purchase tickets to San Diego Theatres' Shows, inquire about information by telephone or fax, or donate to San Diego Theatres, we and/or our business partners may request that you provide certain personally identifiable information, which refers to information that tells us specifically who you are. This information may include your name, phone and fax number, email address, postal address or credit card information (for purchases and donations), and possibly information relating to certain support or patron service issues. We may also collect and keep information regarding your preferred seat locations, show preferences and specific needs.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our web pages such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your internet service provider. We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our web pages such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your internet service provider.
San Diego Theatres uses Google Analytics to help analyze how visitors use our site. They collect standard internet logs and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form, such as: the type of browser and operating system used to access our site; the date and time you access our site; the pages you visit; and if you linked to our Web site from another Web site, the address of that Web site. Google’s ability to use and share information collected about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service and the Google Privacy Policy.
Aggregate Information
We also collect general, non-personal, and statistical information about the use of our websites such as how many visitors visit specific pages, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they click on. This information represents a generic overview of our users' collective viewing habits and allows us to modify information, promotions, offers and/or discounts on products and services based on user traffic and behavior. We collect this information through the use of online tracking technologies including but not limited to "pixels" and "cookies."
Tracking Data
We work with third-party service providers that also collect data on our behalf. Those service providers utilize a retargeting pixel or similar technology, which is placed on our website. The retargeting pixel fires whenever you visit our site, and drops a cookie on your browser. This allows our service providers to anonymously associate the browser to a random ID number in our service providers' databases, and ultimately serve San Diego Theatres' advertisements to you while you browse the rest of the web. Our service providers are able to access the ad inventory on the rest of the web via their integrations and partnerships with ad exchanges and networks. We use Hotjar
in order to better understand our users' needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users' experience and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar is contractually forbidden to sell any of the data collected on our behalf.
How We Use This Information
San Diego Theatres, and our business partner Ticketmaster, use the information you provide about yourself to confirm and process sales transactions, to contact you with questions or communications about your order, to contact you with changes to performance times or performance cancellations, to offer and promote our programs, and services (our email sign-up and information on special events), and to respond to inquiries about our offerings (e.g., questions about tickets and shows). We also use this information to communicate with you and others, such as to notify winners of our contests or drawings, or to contact you about your account with us.
We may also use the information we collect through service providers, including tracking data, to enable you to receive information about our products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you. While we may provide your information to a service provider so that you can receive this information, we do not share your personal information with these service providers.
We may also use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to allow certain service providers to analyze and provide us with statistical information about our customers, including their geographical locations.
How We Share This Information
Except as otherwise described in this policy, we do not sell, rent or trade with third parties any personal information you provide us. We may share your personal information with third parties if one of the following conditions is true:
You allow us to share your personal information.
The disclosure is permitted and/or required by relevant law or is necessary to cooperate with law enforcement.
The disclosure is necessary to protect the interests or safety of San Diego Theatres, visitors to our website, or users of sources of entertainment provided by San Diego Theatres.
The disclosure is reasonably related to the sale or other disposition of all or part of our business or assets.
The information to be disclosed is publicly available.
The party to whom the disclosure is made controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with us.
The disclosure is reasonably necessary for the establishment or maintenance of legal claims.
The disclosure is to persons or entities who provide and perform services for us, provided the disclosure is consistent with the purpose for which the personal information was obtained.
The disclosure is necessary for fraud prevention, detection, and mitigation purposes.
Other Websites
Our websites may contain links to other sites operated by third parties. We do not control such other sites and are not responsible for their content or for their privacy policies. Our inclusion of such links does not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites or of their owners or operators except as specifically disclosed by us. Any information submitted by you directly to these third parties is subject to that third party's privacy policy.
Although we use security that we believe to be appropriate to protect your personal information, we do not guarantee that ours or other websites’ security precautions will protect against, and we expressly disclaim any liability for, any loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information.
Notice to California Residents
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request information regarding the disclosure of their personal information to third parties for third parties direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and you want to make a request, please contact ticketing@sandiegotheatres.org or write to us at 233 A Street, Suite 810, San Diego CA 92101.
Performance Updates
Virtual Event
Sat, Dec 12, 2020 @ 7:00P & Sun, Dec 13, 2020 @ 2:00PThe Hip Hop NutcrackerStreamed + On DemandBuy ticketsMore Info
Virtual Event
Sun, Dec 20, 2020 @ 2:00PJim BrickmanComfort & Joy at Home LIVE! VirtuallyBuy ticketsMore Info
Balboa Theatre
Fri, Mar 5, 2021 @ 7:30PThe Simon and Garfunkel StoryBuy ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Tue, May 5, 2021 @ 7:00PCeltic WomanCelebration – The 15th Anniversary TourBuy TicketsMore Info
Balboa Theatre
Sat, May 8, 2021 @ 8:00P & Sun, May 9, 2021 @ 2:30PGiselleBUY TICKETSMore Info
Civic Theatre
Sun, May 9, 2021 @ 8:00PDead Can DanceA Celebration - Life and WorksBuy ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Tue, May 11 – Sun, May 16, 2021TootsieGet season ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Fri, May 21, 2021 – Sun, May 23, 2021RentBuy ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Tue, Jun 1 – Sun, Jun 6, 2021Pretty Woman The MusicalGet season ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Sun, Jun 20, 2021 @ 8:00PBrit Floyd – World Tour 2021The World's Greatest Pink Floyd ShowBuy ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Tue, Jun 22 – Sun, Jun 27, 2021To Kill A MockingbirdGet season ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Tue, Jul 6 – Sun, Jul 11, 2021My Fair LadyGet season ticketsMore Info
Mon, Jul 19, 2021 @ 7:00PLindsey StirlingArtemis Tour 2021Buy ticketsMore Info
Civic Theatre
Tue, Jul 27, 2021 – Sun, Aug 1, 2021Come From AwayGet season ticketsMore Info
Be in the Know!
Sign Up to Receive our Enews
Be the first to receive news and information on upcoming events and special offers.
Subscribe Here!
Generously Supporting Local Non-ProfitArtistic Productions By
Thank You to OurSupporters & Community Partners!
Support Us
Menu
